<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustenance on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustenance on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy Modernization</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/legacy-modernization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/legacy-modernization/</guid>
      <description>Nobody wants to be saddled with clunky, obsolete legacy applications. After all, the core systems have undergone so many changes over the years that the source code has become defunct and virtually impossible to update.As if that wasn’t bad enough, these apps may not offer good Web integration options, handle data slowly and clumsily, have connectivity and integration problems, offer little room for adding new services and functions and often get little or no support from the companies that created them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/platform/</guid>
      <description>A platform strategy that continues to provide functionality support, performance and technology leadership while making it flexible, affordable and easy to integrate can bring sustainable growth and market leadership. Sustaining existing Platforms while focusing on new product development is a big challenge and also a very critical need for Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology enterprises today. To continue exploration of potential of new disruptive technologies, envision and manage new products under current platform, it is essential that the core IT or engineering team is focused on thinking ahead and not burdened support functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Or Application</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/product-or-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/product-or-application/</guid>
      <description>Technology is constantly evolving and new trends and methodologies keep coming into the market place. As technology grows, user demands also increase and organizations compete with each other to put out products in the market sooner so as to reach the consumers faster. As products evolve, organizations would need to be able to sustain themselves in order to maintain the existing products and also bring out innovative products into the market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>