<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:40:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Netspective sees Wireless capable medical devices with significant software and data integration are the future</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/newsroom/2012-12-03-netspective-sees-wireless-capable-medical-devices-with-significant-software-and-data-integration-are-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/newsroom/2012-12-03-netspective-sees-wireless-capable-medical-devices-with-significant-software-and-data-integration-are-the-future/</guid>
      <description>Summary Netspective, a premium consulting and services firm in the Healthcare and Medical Devices industry announced new approaches for Medical Device firms that would aid in generating revenue and profits, with focus on wireless capable medical devices with software and data integration, to address headwinds they face today.
Story Hundreds of executives and staff in the medical device manufacturing industry gathered in Boston on November 28 to learn about how Wireless capable medical devices could significantly improve patient care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netspective advises medical device manufacturers to get into software, services, and health data integration to help offset revenue losses.</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/newsroom/2012-11-12-netspective-advises-medical-device-manufacturers-to-get-into-software-services-and-health-data-integration-to-help-offset-revenue-losses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 08:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/newsroom/2012-11-12-netspective-advises-medical-device-manufacturers-to-get-into-software-services-and-health-data-integration-to-help-offset-revenue-losses/</guid>
      <description>Summary Netspective, a premium consulting and services firm in Healthcare and Medical Devices industries announced new approaches for Medical Devices firms to grow revenue and profits with focus on software, services and data to offset losses from ACA Excise Tax cost and other headwinds they face today.
Story Hundreds of medical device manufacturer executives, hospital executives, and staff gathered in Boston on November 1 to learn about how “connected devices” can significantly improve patient care and could reduce healthcare costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you cant repeat it, dont bother automating it</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/blog/2008-07-20-if-you-cant-repeat-it-dont-bother-automating-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 23:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/blog/2008-07-20-if-you-cant-repeat-it-dont-bother-automating-it/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#8217;s been plenty of discussion in both literature and general media about &amp;#8220;most software projects failing.&amp;#8221; There are plenty of reasons for failed projects: from inadequate requirements gathering to poor project management to plain incompetence. Some of the problem starts at the C-Suite where projects are actually identified and started &amp;#8212; for asking to automate (presumably with software) something that maybe has no business being automated.
My simple advice to most architects, CTOs, CEOs and CIOs about project management starts with a question: can you methodically and manually repeat the thing you are trying to automate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/access/</guid>
      <description>Business collaboration online is here to stay, but keeping it secure is an ongoing challenge. As identity thieves grow more sophisticated and regulators begin to demand tighter controls — standard access management solutions based on ID provisioning have fallen behind. Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology Industries today need sophisticated solutions in place as they adopt technology for process automation, information and workflow integration between organizations and provide better services and solutions to their customer base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/architecture/</guid>
      <description>A good architecture design should fit in with your legacy systems and products, and should build on what has proven to work. The architecture should also enhance the value of your past investments in technology and processes and exploit opportunities for reuse within the system and across systems. This is especially true in the Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology Industries, wherein regulatory evironment and diverse needs require a well planned scalable solution to be put in place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assemble</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/assemble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/assemble/</guid>
      <description>High-Quality Marketing Content:
The “Open, Sesame!” of Modern Selling
Successful enterprise selling demands content. Lots of it. Brochures, sell sheets, webinars, demonstrations, videos, the list goes on and on. And the amount of it you’ll need to turn prospects into customers might surprise you.
 The CAK helps you find and assemble relevant, high-quality content for your marketing campaigns. It’s the content you’ll need to engage prospects in the all-important first step of the buying process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/business/</guid>
      <description>Business operations in Healthcare and Medical Technology firms are faced with a dire need for financial, operational and clinical performance improvement and optimization. The most successful way to analyze business performance and plan for improvement is by considering 3 essential components: people, process, and technology. Combining and optimizing these 3 components improves financial, operational and clinical performance. Many of the existing processes are not suitable for today’s fast paced and technology centric environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Process Management</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/business-process-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/business-process-management/</guid>
      <description>Having optimized business processes in a regulated industry provides organizations the ability to keep operating costs low while efficiently delivering services or selling products. Aligning an organization’s business processes to your customer’s requirements in a holistic manner is the key tenet to Business Process Management(BPM).
We believe that in order to achieve optimum business efficiency and employee effectiveness, a good understanding, implementation and control of the business processes is essential followed by automation of these processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/clients/</guid>
      <description>Netspective has successfully supported many organizations including Healthcare service providers, Government agencies, Medical Technology firms and other key organizations.
Several large government agencies have engaged Netspective’s Professional Services group to perform architecture and applications assessments for their components and partners. Netspective has used the Enterprise Architecture Planning Turn-key Service to conduct detailed analysis and reviews of existing government applications and to assist with legacy migration planning issues. Some of our largest engagements have been with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/clients/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/deployment/cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/deployment/cloud/</guid>
      <description>Clouds: Driving Down Computing Costs Cloud computing has made quite a stir in the technology industry. Offering a new massively scalable implementation model, cloud computing significantly reduces IT and product costs, optimizes system workload and improves application service delivery for end users and customers. Enterprises in the Healthcare, Government and Medical technology industries are excited by the new dimension available with cloud models, especially the ability to add capabilities without investing in new infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding and Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/coding-and-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/coding-and-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Most Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology firms are able to develop the strategy, planning and architecture of their IT solution or product / platform internally or with outside consulting help in a short time. The next biggest challenge is enabling a large team of skilled resources that bring ability to innovate and refine the ideas, then convert these ideas into physical devices, embedded software or application software with appropriate User Interface and Industrial Design that can beat the business and technology objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/testing/compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/testing/compliance/</guid>
      <description>With limited availability of expertise and dedicated resources in the regulatory compliance space, most organizations are not able to keep up with the ever-changing compliance requirements. Additionally, the regulations across countries vary and so marketing products across geographies will need knowledge and implementation of these country specific regulations. As a result of the challenges involved in complying with the regulations and industry standards like ARRA, HIPAA, HITECH and SOX, enterprises find it difficult to bring their products out into the market in a short period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/content/</guid>
      <description>Organizations today need easy access to relevant and accurate information to perform at peak levels. Providing that information at the time and in the format that it is required is Netspective’s primary concern. Most organizations have a wealth of information both structured and unstructured that has accumulated over time. This information can be a strategic asset if properly collated, categorized and analyzed. The insights gained from such an exercise can provide valuable inputs in the tactical decision making process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curate</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/curate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/curate/</guid>
      <description>Add Your Voice to Make Content Fresh and Interesting
Content marketing is a powerful way to engage your audience with unique, compelling information and ideas. But to be effective, content must be fresh and interesting, chosen carefully and aimed at just the right audience.
The Netspective Content Assembler Kit helps you add your unique voice and views to carefully chosen content. Curated content:
 Adds value and the human touch to content by providing a new perspective—yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/data/</guid>
      <description>Data plays a vital role in the decision making process of an organization. However, Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology firms despite the availability of huge volumes of data, are not able to tap into this valuable resource because of the inconsistency, inaccuracy and incompleteness of it. Management of data involves ensuring the availability of precise, consistent, complete and secure data for the process of analysis, decision making and the overall smooth functioning of an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distribute</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/distribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/distribute/</guid>
      <description>Say Good-bye to Manual Content Distribution The Netspective Content Assembler Kit helps you provide your audience with well-organized, attractive content and distribute it broadly where they want to find it.
CAK tools, services and automated processes eliminate the time and attention you would spend distributing content manually. Use CAK tools and services to:
 Distribute content automatically across social network and traditional Internet channels. Increase your marketing reach by sending content to buyers, stakeholders, channel partners and influencers through social media sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise I.T.</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/enterprise-i-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/enterprise-i-t/</guid>
      <description>Enterprise IT planning is an immensely valuable process. It helps organizations create technically viable, cost effective projects which are easy to execute. It also capitalizes on existing technology investments, allowing enterprises scale their infrastructure to accommodate future upgrades and enhancements. This process can be particularly helpful in government, where systems often cut across agency boundaries and highly varied technologies.
But developing government IT plans is a big job. It requires in-depth technical knowledge, deep expertise in enterprise architecture design and enterprise application Integration, and extensive domain exposure to come up with a comprehensive enterprise IT implementation plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/events/</guid>
      <description>   Upcoming Speaking Events Past Speaking Events     Netspective has been invited to speak at the following upcoming events. Here’s a list of past events we’ve spoken at.   See my conferences on Lanyrd See my conferences on Lanyrd    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fluent-M2M</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/fluent-m2m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/fluent-m2m/</guid>
      <description>Fluent is a healthcare professional and patient centric solution that connects doctors, patients, families and caregivers with an integrated view of the patient data in a secure fashion. Fluent enables this by integration of existing health care systems such as EHR, hospital systems, and patient and content management systems with devices and other applications. Fluent offers a well thought out integration platform for the following enterprises:
 Health care IT and device vendors who offer EHR, Medical equipment and technology solutions Innovators of health care business models who need customized health IT applications looking to create modern EHRs, EMRs, billing service solutions, medical records management, hospital information systems,  The Fluent platform can be deployed on a cloud, as an on-premises solution, and behind a corporate firewall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go To Market</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/go-to-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/go-to-market/</guid>
      <description>All Product or Services firms need to define channels they will use to connect with their clients and generate revenue and profitability. This includes organizational processes such as development, branding strategies and market research and analysis. These processes are essential in guiding sales strategies and carrying customer interactions from initial contact through to fulfillment.
A firm’s Go-To-Market strategy should help them develop and deliver a unique value proposition to their target market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/industries/government/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/industries/government/</guid>
      <description>The rapidity of the economic, political and social changes are driving new ways of governance in U.S. Civilian and Health government agencies especially with constraints being placed on the budget.Some of the most complex challenges today and in the near future are due to financial regulatory oversight reforms, healthcare system reforms, integration of technology and information sharing among law enforcement organizations, enhancing new transportation infrastructure and overhauling the education systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/industries/healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/industries/healthcare/</guid>
      <description>The business of healthcare continues to get more complex as patients, providers, public health payers, regulators, pharmaceuticals, medical devices, pharmacy and technology companies become more connected with each other and directly affect health outcomes.
In order to extend next generation care to patients, healthcare needs to drive rapid reforms with all care associated entities focusing on implementing regulation mandates, bringing workflow integration, creating and implementing new processes and automating them with adequate privacy and security measures to protect patient data to improve clinical intelligence and quality of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IV &amp; V</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/testing/iv-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/testing/iv-v/</guid>
      <description>Before they put software into production, many enterprises conduct an Independent Verification and Validation (IV&amp;amp;V) process to make sure it’s bulletproof.
To conduct IV&amp;amp;V testing, IT and Product organizations in regulated industries like Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology hire third parties with no ties to the professionals who developed the software. These third parties provide a clear, unbiased analysis of software solutions being built. Testers not only verify that software is built correctly, they make sure you’re building the right product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industry and Technology Research</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/industry-and-technology-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/industry-and-technology-research/</guid>
      <description>Your company may offer the best possible solution available for the horizontal market you serve. But if you’d like to reach vertical industries and come across as thought leaders in those sectors, you need specialized expertise.
New business models in delivering patient care cloud computing implications future of smartphones in regulated industries security solutions meeting regulatory requirements integration best practices and solutions. If you need to know about the trends in these areas or others just on the horizon, reading the industry trade press may not be enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/manage/infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>One dramatic change for IT and Technology products has been how Infrastructure is architected, procured and managed across enterprises. This change has occurred across most industry domains, but we see this change just beginning to happen within Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology industries. Enterprises and agencies are opening up to the idea and investing into cloud computing, advanced security, virtualization, Mobility and networking solutions to bring transformational change to their operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/innovation/</guid>
      <description>It takes more than sustaining and improving current value models to operate in today’s Healthcare and Medical Technology business. To build a platform for success in tomorrow’s business environment, new and innovative value models need to be in place as part of the organization’s innovation strategy.
The HITECH Act offers what may be the most significant opportunity that healthcare providers have ever had, to improve patient care and generate revenue substantially not only as a direct outcome of enhanced operational efficiency but also by way of increased Medicare and Medicaid reimbursements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/integration/</guid>
      <description>In the healthcare industry, the integration among the disparate Healthcare delivery systems has been a challenge for some time now. Devices such as the vital sign monitors and infusion pumps use custom protocols that are not designed for interoperability. The want of mandatory standards for these systems result in critical medical information being lost or inaccessible from these systems. Most importantly, the information is not available to the physicians real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy Modernization</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/legacy-modernization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/legacy-modernization/</guid>
      <description>Nobody wants to be saddled with clunky, obsolete legacy applications. After all, the core systems have undergone so many changes over the years that the source code has become defunct and virtually impossible to update.As if that wasn’t bad enough, these apps may not offer good Web integration options, handle data slowly and clumsily, have connectivity and integration problems, offer little room for adding new services and functions and often get little or no support from the companies that created them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/industries/medical-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/industries/medical-technology/</guid>
      <description>The Medical Technology applications and devices space has been one of the fastest growing segments of the global health and wellness industry. However, this industry has been facing serious headwinds lately in trying to maintain profitable and sustained growth. The emerging markets for existing low-end products to new market segments like home based devices and advanced sensor based diagnosis and monitoring solutions bring new opportunities and avenues for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobility</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/mobility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/mobility/</guid>
      <description>The remarkable growth in mobility among the global community has spurred an equivalent increase in the number of mobile devices and networks connecting each other. Mobility is a significant asset in the Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology business. The power of mobility combined with real time connectivity with mission critical systems can give enterprises a tremendous advantage, ability to respond to customers or public effectively and can drastically change the way business is done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operational Excellence with Lean Six Sigma</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/operational-excellence-lean-six-sigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/operational-excellence-lean-six-sigma/</guid>
      <description>Process Improvement using Lean Six Sigma Achieve Operational Excellence in your organization with Netspective’s Lean Six Sigma consulting, training, and implementation services.It focuses on eliminating waste from core operational processes thereby building high quality business processes and increasing efficiency, quality, operational speed and customer satisfaction.
We believe in understanding your current organizational processes before providing you a solution. Our team will work with your staff to streamline processes, improve productivity of your staff, increase your ROI and address your organization’s strategic priorities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/platform/</guid>
      <description>A platform strategy that continues to provide functionality support, performance and technology leadership while making it flexible, affordable and easy to integrate can bring sustainable growth and market leadership. Sustaining existing Platforms while focusing on new product development is a big challenge and also a very critical need for Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology enterprises today. To continue exploration of potential of new disruptive technologies, envision and manage new products under current platform, it is essential that the core IT or engineering team is focused on thinking ahead and not burdened support functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/product/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/product/</guid>
      <description>Medical devices and applications firms today have an opportunity to radically transform their business in the next five years. The growth is expected to be exponential in the U.S., European and emerging markets.This provides an opportunity for Medical Technology firms to re-look at their product portfolio and develop a product and platform strategy that provides for long term and sustained growth on a global scale.
Measuring the past portfolio’s success and use of decision support tools to create forecasts for the future would be the first step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Or Application</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/product-or-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/sustenance/product-or-application/</guid>
      <description>Technology is constantly evolving and new trends and methodologies keep coming into the market place. As technology grows, user demands also increase and organizations compete with each other to put out products in the market sooner so as to reach the consumers faster. As products evolve, organizations would need to be able to sustain themselves in order to maintain the existing products and also bring out innovative products into the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory Compliance &amp; Standards</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/regulatory-compliance-standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/regulatory-compliance-standards/</guid>
      <description>The United States regulatory environment for the Government, Healthcare and Medical technology industries is a robust one with well laid out standards and best practices and sometimes cumbersome and complex requirements. These regulatory mandates are being evaluated and modified today to accommodate the changes affected by technology within these industries. FDA, HIPAA, ICD, ARRA, HITECH and many others have a major role to play in these industries. It is now up to the participants in these industries to understand and leverage them to their business advantage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Management</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/deployment/release-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/deployment/release-management/</guid>
      <description>Clouds: Driving Down Computing Costs Incremental feature addition or requests for new features, feature enhancements and bug corrections trigger the start of a new release cycle. Release management starts off with the start of a new release cycle. A release cycle consists of a broad set of activities encompassing planning, design, testing, build, documentation, configuration and deployment.
Release cycles vary in duration and style based on the kind of software development life cycle followed by an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/research/</guid>
      <description>Marketing Relief for Busy Businesses
The CAK is packed with software, tools and automated processes designed for businesses wanting to take control of their content marketing effort. But this approach might not be the best choice for your organization.
If you want to delegate content marketing chores, we can help. We have the marketing skills, experience and tools that can get results without adding to your crowded schedule.
In each engagement, we put these marketing resources to work for you:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/deployment/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/deployment/security/</guid>
      <description>Enterprises in the Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology industries have a tricky path to walk if they want to maintain their IT or product security. They must create or incorporate new features and technology to provide better customer experience and also respond proactively to security and privacy threats, all while complying with changing regulatory requirements. Enterprises must identify, characterize and neutralize threats before critical systems are compromised and that means continuous monitoring, assessment and quick responses to threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/service/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/technology/</guid>
      <description>The pace of technology change in Healthcare and Medical Technology firms is at its highest now and continues to grow. Successful companies are consistently enhancing their technology strategy by either building new ones or improving their existing strategies or integration as part of M&amp;amp;A. Organizations regularly seek validation of their technology implementations or look for help to bring in new ideas, skills and capabilities that ensures return on their short and long term investments in technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Automation</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/testing/test-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/testing/test-automation/</guid>
      <description>The past few years have seen drastic changes in testing methodologies. Organizations are moving towards test automation in order to save on cost and time. Enterprises are analyzing every phase of the testing life cycle to find out the areas that can be automated by using tools. From initial automated testing strategies where scripting knowledge was required to write scripts to automate testing, the testing industry has gone to making script less testing frameworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.I. &amp; I.D.</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/ui-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/ui-id/</guid>
      <description>At Netspective, we’ve developed user interface design into a fine art, focusing not only on the functions that a software system needs to provide, but also the way in which it presents them to users.
How our UI design process works When we work on your UI design, we follow a thorough, carefully-defined process which produces consistent results.
First, the graphics team creates multiple design templates for review by the client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vendor</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/consulting-services/strategy/vendor/</guid>
      <description>For the Healthcare and Medical Technology industry, executing your strategy efficiently and effectively will require ideas and support from inside your organization and from partners / vendors. As success today and in the future will be enabled by deploying the right technology to automate your processes or for building new products, one needs to put together the right vendor management strategy for all strategic initiatives. To fulfill your vision and execute your business strategy seamlessly, Netspective’s approach to managing partners / vendors can help bring together all resources, processes, best practices and an eco-system that enables selection and effective management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 2.0</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/web-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/web-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Up until a couple of years ago, there were no web sharing sites or applications. Information published or consumed on the web merely consisted of static web pages. This paradigm has undergone a drastic transformation with websites now being areas of active discussion, collaboration and interaction.
This new model of content sharing sites, together called Web 2.0, is drastically changing the way people interact with each other. Web 2.0 opens up a whole new world of possibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Netspective CAK?</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/what-is-cak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/what-is-cak/</guid>
      <description>A Content Marketing Team that Never Sleeps
The Netspective™ Content Assembler Kit is a platform that takes the effort and costs out of launching effective, modern content marketing campaigns. It provides the information and know-how you need to engage customers and prospects and gain their attention and trust.
Think of CAK as your marketing team in a box. Use it to:
 Provide everything you need to assemble, curate and distribute content that will engage current and future customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Attest?</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/attest/why-attest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/attest/why-attest/</guid>
      <description>Because requests for information should be easy on information requester(IR)s, respondents, and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Netspective CAK?</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/why-cak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/why-cak/</guid>
      <description>Have a great product or service but no marketing staff?
It might be time to DIY.
Does enterprise selling come naturally to your staff? Do you have the expertise to pull off a full-bodied content marketing campaign?
If not, no worries! There’s another, proven path to content marketing success.
The Netspective™ Content Assembler Kit helps you avoid the time, costs and hassles of content marketing.
 Guides you through content assembly, curation and distribution tasks, step by step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>