<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CAK on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CAK on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assemble</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/assemble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/assemble/</guid>
      <description>High-Quality Marketing Content:
The “Open, Sesame!” of Modern Selling
Successful enterprise selling demands content. Lots of it. Brochures, sell sheets, webinars, demonstrations, videos, the list goes on and on. And the amount of it you’ll need to turn prospects into customers might surprise you.
 The CAK helps you find and assemble relevant, high-quality content for your marketing campaigns. It’s the content you’ll need to engage prospects in the all-important first step of the buying process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/clients/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curate</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/curate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/curate/</guid>
      <description>Add Your Voice to Make Content Fresh and Interesting
Content marketing is a powerful way to engage your audience with unique, compelling information and ideas. But to be effective, content must be fresh and interesting, chosen carefully and aimed at just the right audience.
The Netspective Content Assembler Kit helps you add your unique voice and views to carefully chosen content. Curated content:
 Adds value and the human touch to content by providing a new perspective—yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distribute</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/distribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/distribute/</guid>
      <description>Say Good-bye to Manual Content Distribution The Netspective Content Assembler Kit helps you provide your audience with well-organized, attractive content and distribute it broadly where they want to find it.
CAK tools, services and automated processes eliminate the time and attention you would spend distributing content manually. Use CAK tools and services to:
 Distribute content automatically across social network and traditional Internet channels. Increase your marketing reach by sending content to buyers, stakeholders, channel partners and influencers through social media sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/research/</guid>
      <description>Marketing Relief for Busy Businesses
The CAK is packed with software, tools and automated processes designed for businesses wanting to take control of their content marketing effort. But this approach might not be the best choice for your organization.
If you want to delegate content marketing chores, we can help. We have the marketing skills, experience and tools that can get results without adding to your crowded schedule.
In each engagement, we put these marketing resources to work for you:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Netspective CAK?</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/what-is-cak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/what-is-cak/</guid>
      <description>A Content Marketing Team that Never Sleeps
The Netspective™ Content Assembler Kit is a platform that takes the effort and costs out of launching effective, modern content marketing campaigns. It provides the information and know-how you need to engage customers and prospects and gain their attention and trust.
Think of CAK as your marketing team in a box. Use it to:
 Provide everything you need to assemble, curate and distribute content that will engage current and future customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Netspective CAK?</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/why-cak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/solutions/cak/why-cak/</guid>
      <description>Have a great product or service but no marketing staff?
It might be time to DIY.
Does enterprise selling come naturally to your staff? Do you have the expertise to pull off a full-bodied content marketing campaign?
If not, no worries! There’s another, proven path to content marketing success.
The Netspective™ Content Assembler Kit helps you avoid the time, costs and hassles of content marketing.
 Guides you through content assembly, curation and distribution tasks, step by step.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>