<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About us on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About us on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.example.com/about-us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/clients/</guid>
      <description>Netspective has successfully supported many organizations including Healthcare service providers, Government agencies, Medical Technology firms and other key organizations.
Several large government agencies have engaged Netspective’s Professional Services group to perform architecture and applications assessments for their components and partners. Netspective has used the Enterprise Architecture Planning Turn-key Service to conduct detailed analysis and reviews of existing government applications and to assist with legacy migration planning issues. Some of our largest engagements have been with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/events/</guid>
      <description>   Upcoming Speaking Events Past Speaking Events     Netspective has been invited to speak at the following upcoming events. Here’s a list of past events we’ve spoken at.   See my conferences on Lanyrd See my conferences on Lanyrd    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/about-us/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/about-us/team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>