<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Netspective - Consulting and Solutions for Regulated IT and Engineering services - Government, Health and Medical Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/architecture/</guid>
      <description>A good architecture design should fit in with your legacy systems and products, and should build on what has proven to work. The architecture should also enhance the value of your past investments in technology and processes and exploit opportunities for reuse within the system and across systems. This is especially true in the Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology Industries, wherein regulatory evironment and diverse needs require a well planned scalable solution to be put in place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding and Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/coding-and-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/coding-and-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Most Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology firms are able to develop the strategy, planning and architecture of their IT solution or product / platform internally or with outside consulting help in a short time. The next biggest challenge is enabling a large team of skilled resources that bring ability to innovate and refine the ideas, then convert these ideas into physical devices, embedded software or application software with appropriate User Interface and Industrial Design that can beat the business and technology objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/integration/</guid>
      <description>In the healthcare industry, the integration among the disparate Healthcare delivery systems has been a challenge for some time now. Devices such as the vital sign monitors and infusion pumps use custom protocols that are not designed for interoperability. The want of mandatory standards for these systems result in critical medical information being lost or inaccessible from these systems. Most importantly, the information is not available to the physicians real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobility</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/mobility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/mobility/</guid>
      <description>The remarkable growth in mobility among the global community has spurred an equivalent increase in the number of mobile devices and networks connecting each other. Mobility is a significant asset in the Healthcare, Government and Medical Technology business. The power of mobility combined with real time connectivity with mission critical systems can give enterprises a tremendous advantage, ability to respond to customers or public effectively and can drastically change the way business is done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.I. &amp; I.D.</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/ui-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/ui-id/</guid>
      <description>At Netspective, we’ve developed user interface design into a fine art, focusing not only on the functions that a software system needs to provide, but also the way in which it presents them to users.
How our UI design process works When we work on your UI design, we follow a thorough, carefully-defined process which produces consistent results.
First, the graphics team creates multiple design templates for review by the client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 2.0</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/web-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/technology-services/development/web-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Up until a couple of years ago, there were no web sharing sites or applications. Information published or consumed on the web merely consisted of static web pages. This paradigm has undergone a drastic transformation with websites now being areas of active discussion, collaboration and interaction.
This new model of content sharing sites, together called Web 2.0, is drastically changing the way people interact with each other. Web 2.0 opens up a whole new world of possibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>